<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="move_flavor_1">"The target is physically pounded with a long tail, a foreleg, or the like." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_2">The target is attacked with a sharp chop. Critical hits land more easily.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_3">The target is slapped repeatedly, back and forth, two to five times in a row.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_4">The target is hit with a flurry of punches that strike two to five times in a row.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_5">"The target is slugged by a punch thrown with muscle-packed power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_6">"Numerous coins are hurled at the target to inflict damage. Money is earned after the battle."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_7">"The target is punched with a fiery fist. This may also leave the target with a burn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_8">"The target is punched with an icy fist. This may also leave the target frozen."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_9">"The target is punched with an electrified fist. This may also leave the target with paralysis."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10">"Hard, pointed, sharp claws rake the target to inflict damage."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_11">"The target is gripped and squeezed from both sides to inflict damage."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_12">"A vicious, tearing attack with big pincers. The target faints instantly if this attack hits."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_13">"In this two-turn attack, blades of wind hit opposing Pokémon on the second turn. Critical hits land more easily."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_14">"A frenetic dance to uplift the fighting spirit. This sharply raises the user’s Attack stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_15">The target is cut with a scythe or claw.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_16">"A gust of wind is whipped up by wings and launched at the target to inflict damage."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_17">"The target is struck with large, imposing wings spread wide to inflict damage."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_18">"The target is blown away, and a different Pokémon is dragged out. In the wild, this ends a battle against a single Pokémon."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_19">"The user flies up into the sky and then strikes its target on the next turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_20">"Things such as long bodies or tentacles are used to bind and squeeze the target for four to five turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_21">"The target is slammed with a long tail, vines, or the like to inflict damage."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_22">"The target is struck with slender, whiplike vines to inflict damage."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_23">"The target is stomped with a big foot. This may also make the target flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_24">"The target is quickly kicked twice in succession using both feet."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_25">"The target is attacked by a kick launched with muscle-packed power."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_26">"The user jumps up high, then strikes with a kick. If the kick misses, the user hurts itself."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_27">"The user lashes out with a quick, spinning kick. This may also make the target flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_28">"Sand is hurled in the target’s face, reducing the target’s accuracy."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_29">"The user sticks out its head and attacks by charging straight into the target. This may also make the target flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_30">"The target is jabbed with a sharply pointed horn to inflict damage."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_31">"The target is jabbed repeatedly with a horn or beak two to five times in a row."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_32">"The user stabs the target with a horn that rotates like a drill. The target faints instantly if this attack hits."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_33">"A physical attack in which the user charges and slams into the target with its whole body."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_34">"The user drops onto the target with its full body weight. This may also leave the target with paralysis."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_35">"A long body, vines, or the like are used to wrap and squeeze the target for four to five turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_36">"A reckless, full-body charge attack for slamming into the target. This also damages the user a little."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_37">"The user rampages and attacks for two to three turns. The user then becomes confused."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_38">"A reckless, life-risking tackle in which the user rushes the target. This also damages the user quite a lot."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_39">"The user wags its tail cutely, making opposing Pokémon less wary and lowering their Defense stats."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_40">"The user stabs the target with a poisonous stinger. This may also poison the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_41">The user damages the target twice in succession by jabbing it with two spikes. This may also poison the target.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_42">"Sharp spikes are shot at the target in rapid succession. They hit two to five times in a row."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_43">"The user gives opposing Pokémon an intimidating leer that lowers the Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_44">"The target is bitten with viciously sharp fangs. This may also make the target flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_45">"The user growls in an endearing way, making opposing Pokémon less wary. This lowers their Attack stats."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_46">"The target is scared off, and a different Pokémon is dragged out. In the wild, this ends a battle against a single Pokémon."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_47">"A soothing lullaby is sung in a calming voice that puts the target into a deep slumber."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_48">"The user generates odd sound waves from its body that confuse the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_49">The target is hit with a destructive shock wave that always inflicts 20 HP damage.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_50">"For four turns, this move prevents the target from using the move it last used."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_51">"Opposing Pokémon are attacked with a spray of harsh acid. This may also lower their Sp. Def stats."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_52">"The target is attacked with small flames. This may also leave the target with a burn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_53">"The target is scorched with an intense blast of fire. This may also leave the target with a burn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_54">"The user cloaks itself and its allies in a white mist that prevents any of their stats from being lowered for five turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_55">The target is blasted with a forceful shot of water.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_56">"The target is blasted by a huge volume of water launched under great pressure."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_57">"The user attacks everything around it by swamping its surroundings with a giant wave."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_58">"The target is struck with an icy-cold beam of energy. This may also leave the target frozen."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_59">"A howling blizzard is summoned to strike opposing Pokémon. This may also leave the opposing Pokémon frozen."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_60">"The target is attacked with a peculiar ray. This may also leave the target confused."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_61">"A spray of bubbles is forcefully ejected at the target. This may also lower the target’s Speed stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_62">"The target is hit with a rainbow-colored beam. This may also lower the target’s Attack stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_63">"The target is attacked with a powerful beam. The user can’t move on the next turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_64">"The target is jabbed with a sharply pointed beak or horn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_65">"A corkscrewing attack that strikes the target with a sharp beak acting as a drill."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_66">"The user grabs the target and recklessly dives for the ground. This also damages the user a little."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_67">"A powerful low kick that makes the target fall over. The heavier the target, the greater the move’s power."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_68">"A retaliation move that counters any physical attack, inflicting double the damage taken."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_69">"The target is thrown using the power of gravity. It inflicts damage equal to the user’s level."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_70">"The target is slugged with a punch thrown at maximum power."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_71">"A nutrient-draining attack. The user’s HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_72">"A nutrient-draining attack. The user’s HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_73">"A seed is planted on the target. It steals some HP from the target every turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_74">"The user’s body grows all at once, raising the Attack and Sp. Atk stats."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_75">"Sharp-edged leaves are launched to slash at opposing Pokémon. Critical hits land more easily."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_76">"In this two-turn attack, the user gathers light, then blasts a bundled beam on the next turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_77">"The user scatters a cloud of poisonous dust that poisons the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_78">"The user scatters a cloud of numbing powder that paralyzes the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_79">"The user scatters a big cloud of sleep-inducing dust around the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_80">"The user attacks the target by scattering petals for two to three turns. The user then becomes confused."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_81">"Opposing Pokémon are bound with silk blown from the user’s mouth that harshly lowers the Speed stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_82">This attack hits the target with a shock wave of pure rage. This attack always inflicts 40 HP damage.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_83">"The target becomes trapped within a fierce vortex of fire that rages for four to five turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_84">"A jolt of electricity crashes down on the target to inflict damage. This may also leave the target with paralysis."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_85">"A strong electric blast crashes down on the target. This may also leave the target with paralysis."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_86">"The user launches a weak jolt of electricity that paralyzes the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_87">"A wicked thunderbolt is dropped on the target to inflict damage. This may also leave the target with paralysis."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_88">"The user picks up and throws a small rock at the target to attack."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_89">"The user sets off an earthquake that strikes every Pokémon around it."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_90">"The user opens up a fissure in the ground and drops the target in. The target faints instantly if this attack hits."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_91">"The user burrows into the ground, then attacks on the next turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_92">"A move that leaves the target badly poisoned. Its poison damage worsens every turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_93">"The target is hit by a weak telekinetic force. This may also confuse the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_94">"The target is hit by a strong telekinetic force. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_95">"The user employs hypnotic suggestion to make the target fall into a deep sleep."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_96">The user meditates to awaken the power deep within its body and raise its Attack stat.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_97">"The user relaxes and lightens its body to move faster. This sharply raises the Speed stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_98">"The user lunges at the target at a speed that makes it almost invisible. This move always goes first."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_99">As long as this move is in use, the power of rage raises the Attack stat each time the user is hit in battle.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_100">"The user switches places with a party Pokémon in waiting, if any. If a wild Pokémon uses this move, it flees."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_101">"The user makes the target see a frightening mirage. It inflicts damage equal to the user’s level."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_102">"The user copies the target’s last move. The move can be used during battle until the Pokémon is switched out."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_103">"An earsplitting screech harshly lowers the target’s Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_104">"By moving rapidly, the user makes illusory copies of itself to raise its evasiveness."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_105">"Restoring its own cells, the user restores its own HP by half of its max HP."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_106">"The user stiffens all the muscles in its body to raise its Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_107">"The user compresses its body to make itself look smaller, which sharply raises its evasiveness."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_108">"The user releases an obscuring cloud of smoke or ink. This lowers the target’s accuracy."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_109">"The target is exposed to a sinister ray that triggers confusion."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_110">"The user withdraws its body into its hard shell, raising its Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_111">"The user curls up to conceal weak spots and raise its Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_112">The user throws up a sturdy wall that sharply raises its Defense stat.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_113">"A wondrous wall of light is put up to reduce damage from special attacks for five turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_114">"The user creates a haze that eliminates every stat change among all the Pokémon engaged in battle."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_115">"A wondrous wall of light is put up to reduce damage from physical attacks for five turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_116">"The user takes a deep breath and focuses so that critical hits land more easily."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_117">The user endures attacks for two turns, then strikes back to cause double the damage taken.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_118">"The user waggles a finger and stimulates its brain into randomly using nearly any move."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_119">The user counters the target by mimicking the target’s last move.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_120">"The user attacks everything around it by causing an explosion. The user faints upon using this move."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_121">A large egg is hurled at the target with maximum force to inflict damage.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_122">"The target is licked with a long tongue, causing damage. This may also leave the target with paralysis."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_123">"The target is attacked with a discharge of filthy gases. This may also poison the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_124">"Unsanitary sludge is hurled at the target. This may also poison the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_125">The user clubs the target with a bone. This may also make the target flinch.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_126">"The target is attacked with an intense blast of all-consuming fire. This may also leave the target with a burn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_127">"The user charges at the target and may make it flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_128">The target is clamped and squeezed by the user’s very thick and sturdy shell for four to five turns.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_129">"Star-shaped rays are shot at opposing Pokémon. This attack never misses."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_130">"The user tucks in its head to raise its Defense stat on the first turn, then rams the target on the next turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_131">Sharp spikes are shot at the target in rapid succession. They hit two to five times in a row.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_132">The target is attacked with long, creeping tentacles, vines, or the like. This may also lower the target’s Speed stat.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_133">"The user temporarily empties its mind to forget its concerns. This sharply raises the user’s Sp. Def stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_134">"The user distracts the target by bending a spoon. This lowers the target’s accuracy."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_135">"The user restores its own HP by up to half of its max HP."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_136">"The target is attacked with a knee kick from a jump. If it misses, the user is hurt instead."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_137">"The user intimidates the target with the pattern on its belly to cause paralysis."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_138">"The user eats the dreams of a sleeping target. The user’s HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_139">"A cloud of poison gas is sprayed in the face of opposing Pokémon, poisoning those it hits."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_140">Round objects are hurled at the target to strike two to five times in a row.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_141">"The user drains the target’s blood. The user’s HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_142">"With a scary face, the user tries to force a kiss on the target. If it succeeds, the target falls asleep."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_143">"A second-turn attack move where critical hits land more easily. This may also make the target flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_144">"The user transforms into a copy of the target right down to having the same move set."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_145">A spray of countless bubbles is jetted at the opposing Pokémon. This may also lower their Speed stat.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_146">The target is hit with rhythmically launched punches. This may also leave the target confused.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_147">"The user scatters bursts of spores that induce sleep."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_148">The user flashes a bright light that cuts the target’s accuracy.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_149">The target is attacked with an odd psychic wave. The attack varies in intensity.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_150">"The user just flops and splashes around to no effect at all…"</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_151">"The user alters its cellular structure to liquefy itself, sharply raising its Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_152">"The target is hammered with a large pincer. Critical hits land more easily."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_153">"The user attacks everything around it by causing atremendous explosion. The user faints upon using this move."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_154">"The target is raked with sharp claws or scythes quickly two to five times in a row."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_155">"The user throws the bone it holds. The bone loops around to hit the target twice—coming and going."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_156">"The user goes to sleep for two turns. This fully restores the user’s HP and heals any status conditions."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_157">"Large boulders are hurled at opposing Pokémon to inflict damage. This may also make the opposing Pokémon flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_158">"The user bites hard on the target with its sharp front fangs. This may also make the target flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_159">The user makes its edges more jagged, which raises its Attack stat.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_160">"The user changes its type to become the same type as the move at the top of the list of moves it knows."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_161">"The user strikes with a simultaneous three-beam attack. This may also burn, freeze, or paralyze the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_162">"The user chomps hard on the target with its sharp front fangs. This cuts the target’s HP in half."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_163">"The target is attacked with a slash of claws or blades. Critical hits land more easily."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_164">"The user creates a substitute for itself using some of its HP. The substitute serves as the user’s decoy."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_165">"This attack is used in desperation only if the user has no PP. It also damages the user a little."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_166">"It enables the user to permanently learn the move last used by the target. Once used, Sketch disappears."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_167">"A consecutive three-kick attack that becomes more powerful with each successful hit."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_168">"The user attacks and steals the target’s held item simultaneously. The user can’t steal anything if it already holds an item."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_169">"The user ensnares the target with thin, gooey silk so it can’t flee from battle." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_170">"The user senses the target’s movements with itsmind to ensure its next attack does not miss the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_171">"A sleeping target sees a nightmare that inflicts some damage every turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_172">"The user cloaks itself in fire and charges at the target. This may also leave the target with a burn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_173">"This attack can be used only if the user is asleep. The harsh noise may also make the target flinch." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_174">"A move that works differently for the Ghost type than for all other types." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_175">"The user flails about aimlessly to attack. The less HP the user has, the greater the move’s power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_176">"The user changes its type to make itself resistant to the type of the attack the opponent used last." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_177">"A vortex of air is shot at the target to inflict damage. Critical hits land more easily." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_178">"The user releases cotton-like spores that cling to the opposing Pokémon, which harshly lowers their Speed stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_179">"An all-out attack that becomes more powerful the less HP the user has." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_180">"The user unleashes its grudge on the move last used by the target by cutting 4 PP from it." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_181">"The user attacks with a chilling gust of powdery snow. This may also freeze the opposing Pokémon." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_182">"Enables the user to protect itself from all attacks. Its chance of failing rises if it is used in succession." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_183">"The user throws a punch at blinding speed. This move always goes first." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_184">"The user frightens the target with a scary face to harshly lower its Speed stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_185">"The user approaches the target disarmingly, then throws a sucker punch. This attack never misses." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_186">"The user kisses the target with a sweet, angelic cuteness that causes confusion." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_187">"The user maximizes its Attack stat in exchange for HP equal to half its max HP." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_188">"Unsanitary sludge is hurled at the target. This may also poison the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_189">"The user hurls mud in the target’s face to inflict damage and lower its accuracy." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_190">"The user attacks by spraying ink in the target’s face or eyes. This may also lower the target’s accuracy." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_191">"The user lays a trap of spikes at the opposingteam’s feet. The trap hurts Pokémon that switch into battle." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_192">"The user fires an electric blast like a cannon to inflict damage and cause paralysis." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_193">"Enables a Ghost-type target to be hit by Normal-and Fighting-type attacks. This also enables an evasive target to be hit." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_194">"After using this move, if the user faints, thePokémon that landed the knockout hit also faints. Its chance of failing rises if it is used in succession." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_195">"Any Pokémon that hears this song faints in three turns, unless it switches out of battle." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_196">"The user attacks with a gust of chilled air. This also lowers the opposing Pokémon’s Speed stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_197">"Enables the user to evade all attacks. Its chance of failing rises if it is used in succession." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_198">"The user strikes the target with a hard bone two to five times in a row." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_199">"The user takes sure aim at the target. This ensures the next attack does not miss the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_200">"The Pokémon rampages and attacks for two to three turns. It then becomes confused." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_201">"A five-turn sandstorm is summoned to hurt all combatants except the Rock, Ground, and Steel types. It raises the Sp. Def stat of Rock types."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_202">"A nutrient-draining attack. The user’s HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_203">"The user endures any attack with at least  1 HP. Its chance of failing rises if it is used in succession." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_204">"The user gazes at the target rather charmingly, making it less wary. This harshly lowers its Attack stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_205">"The user continually rolls into the target over five turns. It becomes more powerful each time it hits." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_206">"A restrained attack that prevents the target from fainting. The target is left with at least  1 HP."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_207">"The user enrages and confuses the target. However, this also sharply raises the target’s Attack stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_208">"The user restores its own HP by up to half of its max HP."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_209">"The user throws an electrically charged tackle at the target. This may also leave the target with paralysis." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_210">"The target is slashed with scythes or claws. This attack becomes more powerful if it hits in succession."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_211">"The target is hit with wings of steel. This may also raise the user’s Defense stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_212">"The user pins the target with a dark, arresting look. The target becomes unable to flee."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_213">"If it is the opposite gender of the user, the target becomes infatuated and less likely to attack."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_214">"While it is asleep, the user randomly uses one of the moves it knows."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_215">"The user makes a soothing bell chime to heal the status conditions of all the party Pokémon."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_216">"This full-power attack grows more powerful the more the user likes its Trainer."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_217">"The user attacks by giving the target a gift with a hidden trap. It restores HP sometimes, however."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_218">"This full-power attack grows more powerful the less the user likes its Trainer."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_219">"The user creates a protective field that prevents status conditions for five turns."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_220">"The user adds its HP to the target’s HP, then equally shares the combined HP with the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_221">"The target is razed with a mystical fire of great intensity. This may also leave the target with a burn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_222">"The user attacks everything around it with a ground-shaking quake. Its power varies."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_223">"The user punches the target with full, concentrated power. This confuses the target if it hits."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_224">"Using its tough and impressive horn, the user rams into the target with no letup."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_225">"The user exhales a mighty gust that inflicts damage. This may also leave the target with paralysis."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_226">"The user switches places with a party Pokémon in waiting and passes along any stat changes."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_227">"The user compels the target to keep using the move it encored for three turns."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_228">"The power of this attack move is doubled if it’s used on a target that’s switching out of battle."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_229">"A spin attack that can also eliminate such moves as Bind, Wrap, Leech Seed, and Spikes."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_230">"A sweet scent that harshly lowers opposing Pokémon’s evasiveness."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_231">"The target is slammed with a steel-hard tail. This may also lower the target’s Defense stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_232">"The target is raked with steel claws. This may also raise the user’s Attack stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_233">"The user attacks last. In return, this throw move never misses."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_234">"The user restores its own HP. The amount of HP regained varies with the weather."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_235">"The user restores its own HP. The amount of HP regained varies with the weather."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_236">"The user restores its own HP. The amount of HP regained varies with the weather."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_237">"A unique attack that varies in type depending on the Pokémon using it."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_238">"The user delivers a double chop with its forearms crossed. Critical hits land more easily."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_239">"The user whips up a vicious tornado to tear at the opposing Pokémon. This may also make them flinch." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_240">"The user summons a heavy rain that falls for five turns, powering up Water-type moves. It lowers the power of Fire-type moves." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_241">"The user intensifies the sun for five turns, powering up Fire-type moves. It lowers the power of Water-type moves."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_242">"The user crunches up the target with sharp fangs. This may also lower the target’s Defense stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_243">"A retaliation move that counters any special attack, inflicting double the damage taken."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_244">"The user hypnotizes itself into copying any stat change made by the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_245">"The user charges the target at blinding speed. This move always goes first."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_246">"The user attacks with a prehistoric power. This may also raise all the user’s stats at once."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_247">"The user hurls a shadowy blob at the target. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_248">"Two turns after this move is used, a hunk of psychic energy attacks the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_249">"The user attacks with a punch. This may also lower the target’s Defense stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_250">"The user traps the target in a violent swirling whirlpool for four to five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_251">"The user gets all party Pokémon to attack the target. The more party Pokémon, the greater the number of attacks."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_252">"This attack hits first and makes the target flinch. It only works the first turn the user is in battle."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_253">"The user attacks in an uproar for three turns. During that time, no Pokémon can fall asleep." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_254">"The user charges up power and raises both its Defense and Sp. Def stats. The move can be used three times." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_255">"The power stored using the move Stockpile is released at once in an attack. The more power is stored, the greater the move’s power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_256">"The power stored using the move Stockpile is absorbed by the user to heal its HP. Storing more power heals more HP." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_257">"The user attacks by exhaling hot breath on the opposing Pokémon. This may also leave those Pokémon with a burn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_258">"The user summons a hailstorm lasting five turns. It damages all Pokémon except the Ice type."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_259">"The user torments and enrages the target, making it incapable of using the same move twice in a row."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_260">"Flattery is used to confuse the target. However, this also raises the target’s Sp. Atk stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_261">"The user shoots a sinister flame at the target to inflict a burn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_262">"The user faints when using this move. In return, this harshly lowers the target’s Attack and Sp. Atk stats."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_263">"This attack move doubles its power if the user is poisoned, burned, or paralyzed."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_264">"The user focuses its mind before launching a punch. This move fails if the user is hit before it is used." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_265">"This attack’s power is doubled when used on a target with paralysis. This also cures the target’s paralysis, however."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_266">"The user draws attention to itself, making all targets take aim only at the user."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_267">"This attack makes use of nature’s power. Its effects vary depending on the user’s environment." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_268">"The user boosts the power of the Electric move it uses on the next turn. This also raises the user’s Sp. Def stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_269">"The target is taunted into a rage that allows it to use only attack moves for three turns."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_270">"The user assists an ally by boosting the power of that ally’s attack."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_271">"The user catches the target off guard and swaps its held item with its own."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_272">"The user mimics the target completely, copying the target’s natural Ability." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_273">"One turn after this move is used, the user’s or its replacement’s HP is restored by half the user’s max HP."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_274">"The user hurriedly and randomly uses a move among those known by ally Pokémon."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_275">"The user lays roots that restore its HP on every turn. Because it’s rooted, it can’t switch out." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_276">"The user attacks the target with great power. However, this also lowers the user’s Attack and Defense stats."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_277">"A barrier reflects back to the target moves like Leech Seed and moves that damage status."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_278">"The user recycles a held item that has been used in battle so it can be used again."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_279">"This attack move’s power is doubled if the user has been hurt by the opponent in the same turn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_280">"The user attacks with a swift chop. It can also break barriers, such as Light Screen and Reflect."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_281">"The user lets loose a huge yawn that lulls the target into falling asleep on the next turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_282">"The user slaps down the target’s held item, and that item can’t be used in that battle. The move does more damage if the target has a held item."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_283">"This attack move cuts down the target’s HP to equal the user’s HP." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_284">"The user attacks opposing Pokémon with explosive fury. The lower the user’s HP, the lower the move’s power."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_285">"The user employs its psychic power to exchange Abilities with the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_286">"If opposing Pokémon know any move also known by the user, they are prevented from using it."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_287">"The user rests to cure itself of poisoning, a burn, or paralysis."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_288">"If the user faints, the user’s grudge fully depletes the PP of the opponent’s move that knocked it out."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_289">"The user steals the effects of any attempts to use a healing or stat-changing move."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_290">"The additional effects of this attack depend upon where it was used."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_291">"Diving on the first turn, the user floats up and attacks on the next turn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_292">"The user lets loose a flurry of open-palmed arm thrusts that hit two to five times in a row." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_293">"The user’s type is changed depending on its environment, such as at water’s edge, in grass, or in a cave."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_294">"The user stares at flashing lights to focus its mind, drastically raising its Sp. Atk stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_295">"The user lets loose a damaging burst of light. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_296">"A mist-like flurry of down envelops and damages the target. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Atk stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_297">"The user covers the target’s body with a mass of down that harshly lowers its Attack stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_298">"The user performs a wobbly dance that confuses the Pokémon around it." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_299">"The user launches a kick that lands a critical hit more easily. This may also leave the target with a burn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_300">"The user kicks up mud on the battlefield. This weakens Electric-type moves for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_301">"The user attacks the target for five turns. The move’s power increases each time it hits." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_302">"The user attacks by wildly swinging its thorny arms. This may also make the target flinch." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_303">"The user slacks off, restoring its own HP by up to half of its max HP." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_304">"The user lets loose a horribly echoing shout with the power to inflict damage." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_305">"The user bites the target with toxic fangs. This may also leave the target badly poisoned." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_306">"The user slashes the target with hard and sharp claws. This may also lower the target’s Defense stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_307">"The target is razed by a fiery explosion. The user can’t move on the next turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_308">"The target is hit with a watery blast. The user can’t move on the next turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_309">"The target is hit with a hard punch fired like a meteor. This may also raise the user’s Attack stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_310">"The user attacks the target while shouting in a startling fashion. This may also make the target flinch."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_311">"This attack move varies in power and type depending on the weather."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_312">"The user releases a soothing scent that heals all status conditions affecting the user’s party."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_313">"The user feigns crying to fluster the target, harshly lowering its Sp. Def stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_314">"The user launches razor-like wind to slash the opposing Pokémon. Critical hits land more easily."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_315">"The user attacks the target at full power. The attack’s recoil harshly lowers the user’s Sp. Atk stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_316">"Enables a Ghost-type target to be hit by Normal- and Fighting-type attacks. This also enables an evasive target to be hit."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_317">"Boulders are hurled at the target. This also lowers the target’s Speed stat by preventing its movement."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_318">"The target is attacked with powdery scales blown by the wind. This may also raise all the user’s stats."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_319">"A horrible sound like scraping metal harshly lowers the target’s Sp. Def stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_320">"The user plays a pleasant melody that lulls the target into a deep sleep."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_321">"The user tickles the target into laughing, reducing its Attack and Defense stats."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_322">"The user absorbs a mystical power from space to raise its Defense and Sp. Def stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_323">"The user spouts water to damage opposing Pokémon. The lower the user’s HP, the lower the move’s power."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_324">"The user attacks with a sinister beam of light. This may also confuse the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_325">"The user throws a punch from the shadows. This attack never misses."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_326">"The user attacks with an odd, unseeable power. This may also make the target flinch."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_327">"The user attacks the target with an uppercut thrown skyward with force."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_328">"The user traps the target inside a harshly raging sandstorm for four to five turns."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_329">"The target faints instantly. It’s less likely to hit the target if it’s used by Pokémon other than Ice types." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_330">"The user attacks by shooting muddy water at the opposing Pokémon. This may also lower their accuracy."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_331">"The user forcefully shoots seeds at the target two to five times in a row."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_332">"The user confounds the target with speed, then slashes. This attack never misses."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_333">"The user launches sharp icicles at the target two to five times in a row."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_334">"The user hardens its body’s surface like iron, sharply raising its Defense stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_335">"The user blocks the target’s way with arms spread wide to prevent escape."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_336">"The user howls loudly to raise its spirit, which raises its Attack stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_337">The user slashes the target with huge sharp claws. </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_338">"The user slams the target with an enormous tree. The user can’t move on the next turn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_339">"The user tenses its muscles to bulk up its body, raising both its Attack and Defense stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_340">"The user bounces up high, then drops on the target on the second turn. This may also leave the target with paralysis."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_341">"The user attacks by hurling a blob of mud at the target. This also lowers the target’s Speed stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_342">"The user hits the target with its tail. This may also poison the target. Critical hits land more easily."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_343">"The user endearingly approaches the target, then steals the target’s held item." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_344">"The user electrifies itself and charges the target. This also damages the user quite a lot. This attack may leave the target with paralysis."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_345">"The user scatters curious leaves that chase the target. This attack never misses."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_346">"The user soaks the battlefield with water. This weakens Fire-type moves for five turns."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_347">"The user quietly focuses its mind and calms its spirit to raise its Sp. Atk and Sp. Def stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_348">"The user handles a sharp leaf like a sword and attacks by cutting its target. Critical hits land more easily."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_349">"The user vigorously performs a mystic, powerful dance that raises its Attack and Speed stats."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_350">"The user hurls hard rocks at the target. Two to five rocks are launched in a row."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_351">"The user strikes the target with a quick jolt of electricity. This attack never misses."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_352">"The user attacks the target with a pulsing blast of water. This may also confuse the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_353">"Two turns after this move is used, a concentrated bundle of light blasts the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_354">"The user attacks the target at full power. The attack’s recoil harshly lowers the user’s Sp. Atk stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_355">"The user lands and rests its body. This move restores the user’s HP by up to half of its max HP." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_356">"Enables Flying-type Pokémon or Pokémon with the Levitate Ability to be hit by Ground-type moves. Flying moves can’t be used." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_357">"Enables a Dark-type target to be hit by Psychic-type attacks. This also enables an evasive target to be hit."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_358">"This attack inflicts big damage on a sleeping target. This also wakes the target up, however."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_359">"The user swings and hits with its strong, heavy fist. It lowers the user’s Speed, however." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_360">"The user tackles the target with a high-speed spin. The slower the user compared to the target, the greater the move’s power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_361">"The user faints. In return, the Pokémon taking its place will have its HP restored and status conditions cured."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_362">"If the target’s HP is half or less, this attack will hit with double the power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_363">"The user draws power to attack by using its held Berry. The Berry determines the move’s type and power."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_364">"This attack hits a target using Protect. This also lifts the effects of the move."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_365">"The user pecks the target. If the target is holding a Berry, the user eats it and gains its effect." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_366">"The user whips up a turbulent whirlwind that ups the Speed stat of the user and its allies for four turns."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_367">"The user applies pressure to stress points, sharply boosting one of its or its allies’ stats."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_368">"The user retaliates with much greater force against the opponent that last inflicted damage on it."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_369">"After making its attack, the user rushes back to switch places with a party Pokémon in waiting." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_370">"The user fights the target up close without guarding itself. This also lowers the user’s Defense and Sp. Def stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_371">"The user stores power, then attacks. If the user moves after the target, this attack’s power will be doubled."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_372">"If the target has already taken some damage in the same turn, this attack’s power is doubled." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_373">"This move prevents the target from using its held item for five turns. Its Trainer is also prevented from using items on it."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_374">"The user flings its held item at the target to attack. This move’s power and effects depend on the item."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_375">"Using its psychic power of suggestion, the user transfers its status conditions to the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_376">The fewer PP this move has, the greater its power.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_377">"For five turns, the user prevents the opposing team from using any moves, Abilities, or held items that recover HP."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_378">"The user powerfully wrings the target. The more HP the target has, the greater the move’s power."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_379">"The user employs its psychic power to switch its Attack stat with its Defense stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_380">"The user hurls up its stomach acids on the target. The fluid eliminates the effect of the target’s Ability." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_381">"The user chants an incantation toward the sky, preventing opposing Pokémon from landing critical hits for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_382">"The user cuts ahead of the target to copy and use the target’s intended move with greater power. This move fails if it isn’t used first." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_383">"The user mimics the move used immediately before it. The move fails if no other move has been used yet." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_384">"The user employs its psychic power to switch changes to its Attack and Sp. Atk stats with the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_385">"The user employs its psychic power to switch changes to its Defense and Sp. Def stats with the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_386">"The more the target has powered up with stat changes, the greater the move’s power."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_387">"This move can be used only after the user has used all the other moves it knows in the battle." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_388">"A seed that causes worry is planted on the target. It prevents sleep by making the target’s Ability Insomnia."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_389">"This move enables the user to attack first. This move fails if the target is not readying an attack." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_390">"The user lays a trap of poison spikes at the feet of the opposing team. The spikes will poison opposing Pokémon that switch into battle."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_391">"The user employs its psychic power to switch stat changes with the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_392">"The user envelops itself in a veil made of water. It regains some HP every turn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_393">"The user levitates using electrically generated magnetism for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_394">"The user cloaks itself in fire and charges the target. This also damages the user quite a lot. This attack may leave the target with a burn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_395">"The target is attacked with a shock wave. This may also leave the target with paralysis." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_396">"The user lets loose a blast of aura power from deep within its body at the target. This attack never misses."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_397">"The user polishes its body to reduce drag. This can sharply raise the Speed stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_398">"The target is stabbed with a tentacle, arm, or the like steeped in poison. This may also poison the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_399">"The user releases a horrible aura imbued with dark thoughts. This may also make the target flinch."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_400">"The user slashes the target the instant an opportunity arises. Critical hits land more easily."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_401">"The user attacks by swinging its tail as if it were a vicious wave in a raging storm."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_402">"The user slams a barrage of hard-shelled seeds down on the target from above."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_403">"The user attacks with a blade of air that slices even the sky. This may also make the target flinch."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_404">"The user slashes at the target by crossing its scythes or claws as if they were a pair of scissors." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_405">"The user generates a damaging sound wave by vibration. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_406">"The target is attacked with a shock wave generated by the user’s gaping mouth." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_407">"The user tackles the target while exhibiting overwhelming menace. This may also make the target flinch."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_408">"The user attacks with a ray of light that sparkles as if it were made of gemstones."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_409">"An energy-draining punch. The user’s HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_410">"The user whirls its fists to send a wave of pure vacuum at the target. This move always goes first." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_411">"The user heightens its mental focus and unleashes its power. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_412">"The user draws power from nature and fires it at the target. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_413">"The user tucks in its wings and charges from a low altitude. This also damages the user quite a lot." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_414">"The user makes the ground under the target erupt with power. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_415">"The user trades held items with the target faster than the eye can follow."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_416">"The user charges at the target using every bit of its power. The user can’t move on the next turn."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_417">"The user stimulates its brain by thinking bad thoughts. This sharply raises the user’s Sp. Atk stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_418">"The user strikes the target with tough punches as fast as bullets. This move always goes first."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_419">"The power of this attack move is doubled if the user has been hurt by the target in the same turn."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_420">"The user flash-freezes chunks of ice and hurls them at the target. This move always goes first."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_421">"The user slashes with a sharp claw made from shadows. Critical hits land more easily."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_422">"The user bites with electrified fangs. This may also make the target flinch or leave it with paralysis."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_423">"The user bites with cold-infused fangs. This may also make the target flinch or leave it frozen."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_424">"The user bites with flame-cloaked fangs. This may also make the target flinch or leave it with a burn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_425">"The user extends its shadow and attacks the target from behind. This move always goes first."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_426">"The user launches a hard-packed mud ball to attack. This may also lower the target’s accuracy."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_427">"The user tears at the target with blades formed by psychic power. Critical hits land more easily." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_428">"The user focuses its willpower to its head and attacks the target. This may also make the target flinch." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_429">"The user lets loose a flash of energy at the target from its polished body. This may also lower the target’s accuracy." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_430">"The user gathers all its light energy and releases it all at once. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_431">"The user attacks the target by smashing into it with incredible force. This may also confuse the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_432">"A strong wind blows away the target’s barriers such as Reflect or Light Screen. This also lowers the target’s evasiveness."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_433">"The user creates a bizarre area in which slower Pokémon get to move first for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_434">"Comets are summoned down from the sky onto the target. The attack’s recoil harshly lowers the user’s Sp. Atk stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_435">"The user strikes everything around it by letting loose a flare of electricity. This may also cause paralysis." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_436">"The user torches everything around it in an inferno of scarlet flames. This may also leave those it hits with a burn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_437">"The user whips up a storm of leaves around the target. The attack’s recoil harshly lowers the user’s Sp. Atk stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_438">"The user violently whirls its vines, tentacles, or the like to harshly lash the target."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_439">"The user launches a huge boulder at the target to attack. The user can’t move on the next turn."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_440">"A slashing attack with a poisonous blade that may also poison the target. Critical hits land more easily."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_441">"The user shoots filthy garbage at the target to attack. This may also poison the target."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_442">"The user slams the target with its steel-hard head. This may also make the target flinch."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_443">"The user launches steel bombs that stick to the target. This attack never misses."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_444">"The user stabs the target from below with sharpened stones. Critical hits land more easily." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_445">"If any opposing Pokémon is the opposite gender of the user, it is charmed, which harshly lowers its Sp. Atk stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_446">"The user lays a trap of levitating stones around the opposing team. The trap hurts opposing Pokémon that switch into battle." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_447">"The user snares the target with grass and trips it. The heavier the target, the greater the move’s power."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_448">"The user attacks the target with sound waves of deafening chatter. This confuses the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_449">"The user releases countless shots of light at the target. This move’s type varies depending on the kind of Plate the user is holding."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_450">"The user bites the target. If the target is holding a Berry, the user eats it and gains its effect." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_451">"The user attacks with an electric charge. The user may use any remaining electricity to raise its Sp. Atk stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_452">"The user slams its rugged body into the target to attack. This also damages the user quite a lot."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_453">"The user lunges at the target at a speed that makes it almost invisible. This move always goes first."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_454">"The user calls out its underlings to pummel the target. Critical hits land more easily."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_455">"The user calls out its underlings to shield its body, raising its Defense and Sp. Def stats."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_456">"The user calls out its underlings to heal it. The user regains up to half of its max HP." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_457">"The user attacks the target with a hazardous, full-power headbutt. This also damages the user terribly."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_458">"The user slams the target with a long tail, vines, or a tentacle. The target is hit twice in a row."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_459">"The user blasts the target with power that distorts even time. The user can’t move on the next turn."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_460">"The user tears the target along with the space around it. Critical hits land more easily."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_461">"The user faints. In return, the Pokémon taking its place will have its status and HP fully restored."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_462">"The target is crushed with great force. The more HP the target has left, the greater this move’s power."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_463">"The target becomes trapped within a maelstrom of fire that rages for four to five turns."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_464">"Opposing Pokémon are dragged into a world of total darkness that makes them sleep." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_465">"The user emits a shock wave from its body to attack its target. This may also harshly lower the target’s Sp. Def stat."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_466">"The user blasts the target with a gust of repulsive wind. This may also raise all the user’s stats at once." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_467">"The user disappears, then strikes the target on the next turn. This move hits even if the target protects itself."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_468">"The user sharpens its claws to boost its Attack stat and accuracy."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_469">"The user and its allies are protected from wide-ranging attacks for one turn."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_470">"The user employs its psychic power to average its Defense and Sp. Def stats with those of the target."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_471">"The user employs its psychic power to average its Attack and Sp. Atk stats with those of the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_472">"The user creates a bizarre area in which Pokémon’s Defense and Sp. Def stats are swapped for five turns."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_473">"The user materializes an odd psychic wave to attack the target. This attack does physical damage." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_474">"The user drenches the target in a special poisonous liquid. This move’s power is doubled if the target is poisoned."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_475">"The user sheds part of its body to make itself lighter and sharply raise its Speed stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_476">"The user scatters a cloud of irritating powder to draw attention to itself. Opponents aim only at the user."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_477">"The user makes the target float with its psychic power. The target is easier to hit for three turns."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_478">"The user creates a bizarre area in which Pokémon’s held items lose their effects for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_479">"The user throws a stone or similar projectile to attack an opponent. A flying Pokémon will fall to the ground when it’s hit."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_480">"The user strikes the target with a fierce blow. This attack always results in a critical hit." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_481">"The user attacks the target with a bursting flame. The bursting flame damages Pokémon next to the target as well." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_482">"The user strikes everything around it by swamping the area with a giant sludge wave. This may also poison those hit." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_483">"The user lightly performs a beautiful, mystic dance. This boosts the user’s Sp. Atk, Sp. Def, and Speed stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_484">"The user slams into the target with its heavy body. The more the user outweighs the target, the greater the move’s power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_485">"Using an odd shock wave, the user inflicts damage on any Pokémon of the same type in the area around it." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_486">"The user hurls an electric orb at the target. The faster the user is than the target, the greater the move’s power."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_487">"The user shoots a torrent of water at the target and changes the target’s type to Water." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_488">"Cloaking itself in flame, the user attacks. Then, building up more power, the user raises its Speed stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_489">"The user coils up and concentrates. This raises its Attack and Defense stats as well as its accuracy."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_490">"The user makes a swift attack on the target’s legs, which lowers the target’s Speed stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_491">"The user spits fluid that works to melt the target. This harshly lowers the target’s Sp. Def stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_492">"The user turns the target’s power against it. The higher the target’s Attack stat, the greater the damage it deals."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_493">"The user’s mysterious psychic wave changes the target’s Ability to Simple." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_494">"The user dances with an odd rhythm that compels the target to mimic it, making the target’s Ability the same as the user’s."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_495">"The user helps the target and makes it use its move right after the user." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_496">"The user attacks the target with a song. Others can join in the Round to increase the power of the attack." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_497">"The user attacks the target with an echoing voice. If this move is used every turn, its power is increased." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_498">"Looking for an opening, the user strikes consistently. The target’s stat changes don’t affect this attack’s damage."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_499">"The user attacks by throwing a clump of special mud. All stat changes are returned to normal." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_500">"The user attacks the target with stored power. The more the user’s stats are raised, the greater the move’s power."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_501">"The user protects itself and its allies from priority moves."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_502">"The user teleports using a strange power and switches places with one of its allies."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_503">"The user shoots boiling hot water at its target. This may also leave the target with a burn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_504">"The user breaks its shell, which lowers Defense and Sp. Def stats but sharply raises its Attack, Sp. Atk, and Speed stats."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_505">"The user emits a healing pulse that restores the target’s HP by up to half of its max HP."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_506">"This relentless attack does massive damage to a target affected by status conditions." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_507">"The user takes the target into the sky, then drops it during the next turn. The target cannot attack while in the sky."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_508">"The user rotates its gears, raising its Attack stat and sharply raising its Speed stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_509">"The target is thrown, and a different Pokémon is dragged out. In the wild, this ends a battle against a single Pokémon." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_510">"The user attacks opposing Pokémon with fire. If a Pokémon is holding a certain item, such as a Berry, the item becomes burned up and unusable."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_511">"The user suppresses the target and makes its move go last."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_512">"The user nimbly strikes the target. If the user is not holding an item, this attack inflicts massive damage."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_513">"The user reflects the target’s type, making it the same type as the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_514">"The user gets revenge for a fainted ally. If an ally fainted in the previous turn, this move’s power is increased."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_515">"The user risks everything to attack its target. The user faints but does damage equal to its HP."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_516">"The user passes its held item to the target when the target isn’t holding an item."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_517">"The user attacks by engulfing the target in an intense fire. This leaves the target with a burn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_518">"A column of water strikes the target. When combined with its fire equivalent, its power increases and a rainbow appears." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_519">"A column of fire hits the target. When used with its grass equivalent, its power increases and a vast sea of fire appears." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_520">"A column of grass hits the target. When used with its water equivalent, its power increases and a vast swamp appears."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_521">"After making its attack, the user rushes back to switch places with a party Pokémon in waiting."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_522">"While resisting, the user attacks the opposing Pokémon. This lowers the Sp. Atk stat of those hit." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_523">"The user strikes everything around it by stomping down on the ground. This lowers the Speed stat of those hit."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_524">"The user blows its cold breath on the target. This attack always results in a critical hit."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_525">"The target is knocked away, and a different Pokémon is dragged out."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_526">"The user is roused, and its Attack and Sp. Atk stats increase."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_527">"The user attacks and captures opposing Pokémon using an electric net. This lowers their Speed stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_528">"The user shrouds itself in electricity and smashes into its target. This also damages the user a little."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_529">"The user crashes into its target while rotating its body like a drill. Critical hits land more easily."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_530">"The user attacks its target by hitting it with brutal strikes. The target is hit twice in a row." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_531">"The user unleashes a vicious blow after its cute act makes the target less wary. This may also make the target flinch." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_532">"The user drains the target’s energy with its horns. The user’s HP is restored by half the damage taken by the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_533">"The user attacks by slicing with a long horn. The target’s stat changes don’t affect this attack’s damage."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_534">"The user cuts its target with sharp shells. This may also lower the target’s Defense stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_535">"The user slams its target with its flame-covered body. The more the user outweighs the target, the greater the move’s power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_536">"The user attacks its target by encircling it in sharp leaves. This attack may also lower the target’s accuracy." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_537">"The user crushes its target by rolling over the target with its rolled-up body. This may also make the target flinch." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_538">"The user protects itself by wrapping its body in soft cotton, which drastically raises the user’s Defense stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_539">"The user lets loose a pitch-black shock wave at its target. This may also lower the target’s accuracy."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_540">"The user materializes an odd psychic wave to attack the target. This attack does physical damage."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_541">"The user attacks by striking the target with its hard tail. It hits the target two to five times in a row." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_542">"The user attacks by wrapping its opponent in a fierce wind that flies up into the sky. This may also confuse the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_543">"The user charges its head into its target, using its powerful guard hair. This also damages the user a little."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_544">"The user attacks by throwing steel gears at its target twice." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_545">"The user torches everything around it in an inferno of scarlet flames. This may also leave those it hits with a burn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_546">"The user fires a beam of light at its target. The move’s type changes depending on the Drive the user holds." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_547">"The user sings an ancient song and attacks by appealing to the hearts of the listening opposing Pokémon. This may also induce sleep." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_548">"The user cuts with its long horn. The odd power contained in the horn does physical damage to the target."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_549">"The user attacks by blowing freezing cold air at opposing Pokémon. This lowers their Speed stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_550">"The user surrounds itself with a great amount of electricity and charges its target. This may also leave the target with paralysis." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_551">"The user attacks by engulfing the target in an intense, yet beautiful, blue flame. This may also leave the target with a burn."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_552">"Cloaked in flames, the user dances and flaps its wings. This may also raise the user’s Sp. Atk stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_553">"On the second turn, the user hits the target with electrically charged ice. This may also leave the target with paralysis." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_554">"On the second turn, an ultracold, freezing wind surrounds the target. This may leave the target with a burn."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_555">"The user yells as if it’s ranting about something, which lowers the Sp. Atk stat of opposing Pokémon."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_556">"The user attacks by harshly dropping large icicles onto the target. This may also make the target flinch." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_557">"With a hot flame on its forehead, the user hurls itself at its target. This lowers the user’s Defense, Sp. Def, and Speed stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_558">"The user brings down a giant flame. This move’s power is increased when influenced by an enormous lightning bolt." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_559">"The user throws down a giant lightning bolt. This move’s power is increased when influenced by an enormous flame."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_560">"The user dives down onto the target from the sky. This move is Fighting and Flying type simultaneously." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_561">"Using a pulled-up mat as a shield, the user protects itself and its allies from damaging moves. This does not stop status moves."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_562">"The user lets out a damaging belch at the target. The user must eat a held Berry to use this move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_563">"Tilling the soil, the user makes it easier for plants to grow. This raises the Attack and Sp. Atk stats of Grass-type Pokémon." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_564">"The user weaves a sticky net around the opposing team, which lowers their Speed stat upon switching into battle."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_565">"When the user knocks out a target with this move, the user’s Attack stat rises drastically." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_566">"The user vanishes somewhere, then strikes the target on the next turn. This move hits even if the target protects itself."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_567">"The user takes the target trick-or-treating. This adds Ghost type to the target’s type."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_568">"Letting out a noble roar, the user intimidates the target and lowers its Attack and Sp. Atk stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_569">"The user disperses electrically charged particles, which changes Normal-type moves to Electric-type moves."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_570">"The user attacks everything around it. The user’s HP is restored by half the damage taken by those hit."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_571">"The user puts a forest curse on the target. The target is now Grass type as well."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_572">"The user stirs up a violent petal blizzard and attacks everything around it." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_573">"The user rapidly cools the target. This may also leave the target frozen. This move is super effective on Water types." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_574">"Letting out a charming cry, the user does emotional damage to opposing Pokémon. This attack never misses." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_575">"With a parting threat, the user lowers the target’s Attack and Sp. Atk stats. Then it switches with a party Pokémon." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_576">"All stat changes affecting the target turn topsy-turvy and become the opposite of what they were." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_577">"The user steals the target’s HP with a kiss. The user’s HP is restored by over half of the damage taken by the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_578">"The user protects itself and its allies from status moves with a mysterious power. This does not stop moves that do damage."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_579">"The user raises the Defense stat of all Grass-type Pokémon in battle with a mysterious power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_580">"The user turns the ground to grass for five turns. This restores the HP of Pokémon on the ground a little every turn and powers up Grass-type moves." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_581">"This protects Pokémon on the ground from status conditions and halves damage from Dragon-type moves for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_582">"If the target is electrified before it uses a move during that turn, the target’s move becomes Electric type."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_583">"The user plays rough with the target and attacks it. This may also lower the target’s Attack stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_584">"The user stirs up a fairy wind and strikes the target with it." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_585">"Borrowing the power of the moon, the user attacks the target. This may also lower the target’s Sp. Atk stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_586">"The user attacks everything around it with the destructive power of a terrible, explosive sound."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_587">"By locking down the battlefield, the user keeps all Pokémon from fleeing during the next turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_588">"The user takes a defensive stance while it protects itself from damage. It also harshly lowers the Attack stat of any attacker who makes direct contact." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_589">"The user and the target become friends, and the target loses its will to fight. This lowers the target’s Attack stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_590">"The user tells the target a secret, and the target loses its ability to concentrate. This lowers the target’s Sp. Atk stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_591">"The user whips up a storm of diamonds to damage opposing Pokémon. This may also sharply raise the user’s Defense stat."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_592">"The user immerses the target in superheated steam. This may also leave the target with a burn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_593">"Using a hyperspace hole, the user appears right next to the target and strikes. This also hits a target using a move such as Protect or Detect."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_594">"The user hits the target with throwing stars two to five times in a row. This move always goes first."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_595">"The user attacks by breathing a special, hot fire. This also lowers the target’s Sp. Atk stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_596">"In addition to protecting the user from attacks, this move also damages any attacker who makes direct contact."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_597">"The user raises the Sp. Def stat of an ally Pokémon by using a mysterious aroma." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_598">"The user’s body generates an eerie impulse. Exposing the target to it harshly lowers the target’s Sp. Atk stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_599">"Opposing Pokémon are drenched in an odd poisonous liquid. This lowers the Attack, Sp. Atk, and Speed stats of a poisoned target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_600">"The user covers the target in a combustible powder. If the target uses a Fire-type move, the powder explodes and damages the target."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_601">"The user absorbs energy and sharply raises its Sp. Atk, Sp. Def, and Speed stats on the next turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_602">"The user manipulates magnetic fields, which raises the Defense and Sp. Def stats of ally Pokémon with the Plus or Minus Ability."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_603">"Using Happy Hour doubles the amount of prize money received after battle." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_604">"The user electrifies the ground for five turns, powering up Electric-type moves. Pokémon on the ground no longer fall asleep."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_605">"The user damages opposing Pokémon by emitting a powerful flash." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_606">The Pokémon congratulates you on your special day!  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_607">"The user and an ally hold hands. This makes them very happy." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_608">"The user stares at the target with its baby-doll eyes, which lowers its Attack stat. This move always goes first." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_609">"The user attacks by nuzzling its electrified cheeks against the target. This also leaves the target with paralysis."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_610">"The user holds back when it attacks, and the target is left with at least  1 HP."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_611">"The target is infested and attacked for four to five turns. The target can’t flee during this time."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_612">"Striking opponents over and over makes the user’s fists harder. Hitting a target raises the Attack stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_613">"The user absorbs its target’s HP. The user’s HP is restored by over half of the damage taken by the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_614">"This move also hits opposing Pokémon that are in the air. Those Pokémon are knocked down to the ground."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_615">"The user attacks with a wave that crawls along the ground. Those it hits can’t flee from battle."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_616">"The user gathers the energy of the land and focuses that power on opposing Pokémon to damage them." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_617">"Drawing power from the Eternal Flower, the user fires a powerful beam of light. This also damages the user quite a lot."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_618">"The user attacks opposing Pokémon with countless beams of light that glow a deep and brilliant blue."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_619">"The user attacks opposing Pokémon by manifesting the power of the land in fearsome blades of stone." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_620">"After soaring upward, the user attacks its target by dropping out of the sky at high speeds. But it lowers its own Defense and Sp. Def stats in the process." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_621">"Using its many arms, the user unleashes a barrage of attacks that ignore the effects of moves like Protect and Detect. But the user’s Defense stat falls." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_622">"The user builds up its momentum using its Z-Power and crashes into the target at full speed. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_623">"The user rams an energy orb created by its Z-Power into the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_624">"The user rams an energy orb created by its Z-Power into the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_625">"The user soars up with its Z-Power and plummets toward the target at full speed. The power varies, depending on the original move."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_626">"The user soars up with its Z-Power and plummets toward the target at full speed. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_627">"The user creates a poisonous swamp using its Z-Power and sinks the target into it at full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_628">"The user creates a poisonous swamp using its Z-Power and sinks the target into it at full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_629">"The user burrows deep into the ground and slams into the target with the full force of its Z-Power. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_630">"The user burrows deep into the ground and slams into the target with the full force of its Z-Power. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_631">"The user summons a huge rock mountain using its Z-Power and drops it onto the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_632">"The user summons a huge rock mountain using its Z-Power and drops it onto the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_633">"The user binds the target with full force with threads of silk that the user spits using its Z-Power. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_634">"The user binds the target with full force with threads of silk that the user spits using its Z-Power. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_635">"Deep-seated grudges summoned by the user’s Z-Power trap the target. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_636">"Deep-seated grudges summoned by the user’s Z-Power trap the target. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_637">"The user spins very fast and rams into the target with the full force of its Z-Power. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_638">"The user spins very fast and rams into the target with the full force of its Z-Power. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_639">"The user breathes a stream of intense fire toward the target with the full force of its Z-Power. The power varies depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_640">"The user breathes a stream of intense fire toward the target with the full force of its Z-Power. The power varies depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_641">"The user creates a huge whirling current using its Z-Power to swallow the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_642">"The user creates a huge whirling current using its Z-Power to swallow the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_643">"The user collects energy from plants using its Z-Power and attacks the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_644">"The user collects energy from plants using its Z-Power and attacks the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_645">"The user hits the target with a powerful electric current collected by its Z-Power. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_646">"The user hits the target with a powerful electric current collected by its Z-Power. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_647">"The user controls the target with its Z-Power and hurts the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_648">"The user controls the target with its Z-Power and hurts the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_649">"The user dramatically drops the temperature using its Z-Power and freezes the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_650">"The user dramatically drops the temperature using its Z-Power and freezes the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_651">"The user materializes its aura using its Z-Power and attacks the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_652">"The user materializes its aura using its Z-Power and attacks the target with full force. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_653">"The user gathers dark energy using its Z-Power and sucks the target into it. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_654">"The user gathers dark energy using its Z-Power and sucks the target into it. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_655">"The user creates a very charming space using its Z-Power and totally toys with the target. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_656">"The user creates a very charming space using its Z-Power and totally toys with the target. The power varies, depending on the original move." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_657">"The user, Pikachu, surrounds itself with the maximum amount of electricity using its Z-Power and pounces on its target with full force." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_658">"The user, Pikachu, surrounds itself with the maximum amount of electricity using its Z-Power and pounces on its target with full force."   </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_659">"The user regains up to half of its max HP. It restores more HP in a sandstorm." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_660">"Although this move has great power, it only works the first turn each time the user enters battle."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_661">"In addition to protecting the user from attacks, this move also poisons any attacker that makes direct contact."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_662">"The user attacks while simultaneously stitching the target’s shadow to the ground to prevent the target from escaping."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_663">"The user swings both arms and hits the target.The target’s stat changes don’t affect this attack’s damage."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_664">"The user bursts into song, emitting many bubbles. Any Pokémon suffering from a burn will be healed by the touch of these bubbles."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_665">"The user swings and hits with its strong, heavy fist. It lowers the user’s Speed, however."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_666">"The user restores the target’s HP by up to half of its max HP. It restores more HP when the terrain is grass." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_667">"The user fiercely attacks the target using its entire body."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_668">"The user restores its HP by the same amount as the target’s Attack stat. It also lowers the target’s Attack stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_669">"In this two-turn attack, the user gathers light and fills a blade with the light’s energy, attacking the target on the next turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_670">The user attacks by pelting the target with leaves.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_671">"The user shines a spotlight on the target so that only the target will be attacked during the turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_672">"The user shoots poisonous threads to poison the target and lower the target’s Speed stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_673">"The user concentrates intensely. The attack on the next turn always results in a critical hit."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_674">"The user engages its gears to raise the Attack and Sp. Atk stats of ally Pokémon with the Plus or Minus Ability."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_675">"The user attacks the target’s throat, and the resultant suffering prevents the target from using moves that emit sound for two turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_676">"The user attacks the enemy with a pollen puff that explodes. If the target is an ally, it gives the ally a pollen puff that restores its HP instead." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_677">"The user entangles the target with its anchor chain while attacking. The target becomes unable to flee."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_678">"This protects Pokémon on the ground from priority moves and powers up Psychic-type moves for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_679">"The user makes a lunge at the target, attacking with full force. This also lowers the target’s Attack stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_680">"The user strikes the target with a burning lash. This also lowers the target’s Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_681">"The user boasts its strength and attacks the target. The more the user’s stats are raised, the greater the move’s power."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_682">"To inflict massive damage, the user burns itself out. After using this move, the user will no longer be Fire type."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_683">The user exchanges Speed stats with the target. </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_684">"The user stabs the target with a sharp horn. This attack never misses." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_685">"The user heals the target’s status condition. If the move succeeds, it also restores the user’s own HP." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_686">"The user attacks the target by dancing very hard. The user’s type determines the type of this move."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_687">"If the Pokémon the user has inflicted damage on have already used their moves, this move eliminates the effect of the target’s Ability." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_688">"The user lands an intense kick of tropical origins on the target. This also lowers the target’s Attack stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_689">"The user instructs the target to use the target’s last move again."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_690">"The user first heats up its beak, and then it attacks the target. Making direct contact with the Pokémon while it’s heating up its beak results in a burn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_691">"The user rubs the scales on its entire body and makes a huge noise to attack opposing Pokémon. The user’s Defense stat goes down after the attack." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_692">"The user uses its body like a hammer to attack the target and inflict damage." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_693">"The user swings its body around violently to inflict damage on everything in its vicinity."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_694">"This move reduces damage from physical and special moves for five turns. This can be used only in a hailstorm."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_695">"The user, Decidueye, creates countless arrows using its Z-Power and shoots the target with full force." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_696">"The user, Incineroar, strengthens its body using its Z-Power and crashes into the target with full force." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_697">"The user, Primarina, summons a massive amount of water using its Z-Power and attacks the target with full force." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_698">"The user, the Land Spirit Pokémon, obtains Alola’s energy using its Z-Power and attacks the target with full force. This reduces the target’s HP greatly." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_699">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Marshadow, punches and kicks the target consecutively with full force." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_700">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Alolan Raichu, attacks the target with full force. This move leaves the target with paralysis." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_701">"Z-Power brings out the true capabilities of the user, Snorlax. The Pokémon moves its enormous body energetically and attacks the target with full force." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_702">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Eevee, gets energy from its evolved friends and boosts its stats sharply." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_703">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Mew, attacks the target with full force. The terrain will be charged with psychic energy." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_704">"The user sets a shell trap. If the user is hit by a physical move, the trap will explode and inflict damage on opposing Pokémon." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_705">"The user unleashes a strong beam. The attack’s recoil harshly lowers the user’s Sp. Atk stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_706">"The user bites the target with its psychic capabilities. This can also destroy Light Screen and Reflect."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_707">"Driven by frustration, the user attacks the target. If the user’s previous move has failed, the power of this move doubles."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_708">"The user attacks by beating the target with a bone that contains a spirit. This may also lower the target’s Defense stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_709">"The user smashes into the target at high speed. This move always goes first."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_710">"The user slams into the target using a full-force blast of water. This may also lower the target’s Defense stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_711">"The user shoots powerful lasers using the power of a prism. The user can’t move on the next turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_712">"The user hides in the target’s shadow, steals the target’s stat boosts, and then attacks."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_713">"The user slams into the target with the force of a meteor. This move can be used on the target regardless of its Abilities."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_714">"The user emits a sinister ray to attack the target. This move can be used on the target regardless of its Abilities."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_715">"The user gets teary eyed to make the target lose its combative spirit. This lowers the target’s Attack and Sp. Atk stats."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_716">"A strong electric blast crashes down on the target, giving it an electric shock. This may also make the target flinch." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_717">"The user hits the target with the force of nature. It halves the target’s HP." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_718">"Cloaking itself in high energy, the user slams into the target. The memory held determines the move’s type."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_719">"The user, Pikachu wearing a cap, powers up a jolt of electricity using its Z-Power and unleashes it. Critical hits land more easily." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_720">"The user attacks everything around it by causing its own head to explode. This also damages the user."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_721">"The user attacks with electrically charged fists. This move changes Normal-type moves to Electric-type moves."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_722">"The user attacks a target with a pillar of light. This move inflicts Attack or Sp. Atk damage—whichever stat is higher for the user."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_723">"This attack inflicts Attack or Sp. Atk damage— whichever stat is higher for the user, Necrozma. This move ignores the target’s Ability." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_724">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Solgaleo, attacks the target with full force. This move can ignore the effect of the target’s Ability." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_725">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Lunala, attacks the target with full force. This move can ignore the effect of the target’s Ability."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_726">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Mimikyu, punches the target with full force." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_727">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Lycanroc, attacks the target with full force. This move negates the effect on the battlefield." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_728">"After obtaining Z-Power, the user, Kommo-o, attacks the opposing Pokémon with full force. This move boosts the user’s stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_729">"The user attacks the target with bursts of electricity at high speed. This move always goes first and results in a critical hit." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_730">"The user charges a huge wave with electricity and hits the opposing Pokémon with the wave. This may also leave the opposing Pokémon with paralysis." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_731">"The user floats in the air, and then dives at a steep angle to attack the target. This may also make the target flinch."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_732">"The more Pikachu loves its Trainer, the greater the move’s power. It never misses." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_733">"The user attacks by shooting water bubbles at the target. It then absorbs water and restores its HP by half the damage taken by the target."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_734">"The user shoots a jolt of electricity to attack the target. This also leaves the target with paralysis."  </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_735">"The user cloaks itself in fire and charges at the target. This also leaves the target with a burn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_736">"The user bombards the target with telekinetic force.A wondrous wall of light is put up to weaken the power of the opposing Pokémon’s special moves." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_737">"The user acts bad and attacks the target. A wondrous wall of light is put up to weaken the power of the opposing Pokémon’s physical moves." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_738">"The user grows a gigantic stalk that scatters seeds to attack the target. The seeds drain the target’s HP every turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_739">"The user attacks with a crystal made of cold frozen haze. It eliminates every stat change among all the Pokémon engaged in battle." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_740">"The user attacks the target by wrapping it with a whirlwind of an overpowering scent. This also heals all status conditions of the user’s party." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_741">"The more Eevee loves its Trainer, the greater the move’s power. It never misses." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_742">"The user rotates, centering the hex nut in its chest, and then strikes with its arms twice in a row. This may also make the target flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_743">"This move enables the user to protect itself from all attacks. Its chance of failing rises if it is used in succession."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_744">"The user unleashes a strong beam from its core. This move deals twice the damage if the target is Dynamaxed."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_745">"The user ignores the effects of opposing Pokémon’s moves and Abilities that draw in moves, allowing this move to hit the chosen target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_746">"This move prevents the user and the target from switching out until either of them faints. The effect goes away if either of the Pokémon leaves the field." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_747">"The user eats its held Berry, then sharply raises its Defense stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_748">"This move raises all the user’s stats but prevents the user from switching out or fleeing."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_749">"The user pours sticky tar over the target, lowering the target’s Speed stat. The target becomes weaker to Fire-type moves." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_750">"The user scatters a cloud of magic powder that changes the target to Psychic type." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_751">"The user attacks twice using Dreepy. If there are two targets, this move hits each target once." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_752">"The user has teatime with all the Pokémon in the battle. Each Pokémon eats its held Berry."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_753">"The user locks the target in and prevents it from fleeing. This move also lowers the target’s Defense and Sp. Def every turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_754">"The user stabs the target with its electrified beak. If the user attacks before the target, the power of this move is doubled."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_755">"The user rends the target with its hard gills. If the user attacks before the target, the power of this move is doubled." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_756">"With its mysterious power, the user swaps the effects on either side of the field." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_757">"This is a Fire-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. The user intensifies the sun for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_758">"This is a Bug-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This lowers the target’s Sp. Atk stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_759">"This is an Electric-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. The user turns the ground into Electric Terrain for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_760">"This is a Normal-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This lowers the target’s Speed stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_761">"This is a Fighting-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This raises ally Pokémon’s Attack stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_762">"This is a Ghost-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This lowers the target’s Defense stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_763">"This is an Ice-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. The user summons a hailstorm lasting five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_764">"This is a Poison-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This raises ally Pokémon’s Sp. Atk stats."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_765">"This is a Water-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. The user summons a heavy rain that falls for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_766">"This is a Flying-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This raises ally Pokémon’s Speed stats."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_767">"This is a Fairy-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. The user turns the ground into Misty Terrain for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_768">"This is a Dragon-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This lowers the target’s Attack stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_769">"This is a Psychic-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. The user turns the ground into Psychic Terrain for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_770">"This is a Rock-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. The user summons a sandstorm lasting five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_771">"This is a Ground-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This raises ally Pokémon’s Sp. Def stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_772">"This is a Dark-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This lowers the target’s Sp. Def stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_773">"This is a Grass-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. The user turns the ground into Grassy Terrain for five turns." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_774">"This is a Steel-type attack Dynamax Pokémon use. This raises ally Pokémon’s Defense stats."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_775">The user raises all its stats by using some of its HP.</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_776">"The user attacks by slamming its body into the target. The higher the user’s Defense, the more damage it can inflict on the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_777">"The user sharply raises the target’s Attack and Sp. Atk stats by decorating the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_778">"The user plays its drum, controlling the drum’s roots to attack the target. This also lowers the target’s Speed stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_779">"The user snares the target in a snap trap for four to five turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_780">"The user attacks by igniting a small stone and launching it as a fiery ball at the target. This may also leave the target with a burn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_781">"The user becomes a gigantic sword and cuts the target. This move deals twice the damage if the target is Dynamaxed."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_782">"The user becomes a gigantic shield and slams into the target. This move deals twice the damage if the target is Dynamaxed."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_783">"Morpeko attacks and raises its Speed with the energy stored in its cheeks. This move’s type changes depending on the user’s form." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_784">"The user swings its tough tail wildly and attacks opposing Pokémon. This also lowers their Attack stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_785">"The user attacks the target by poking it with a sharply pointed branch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_786">"The user attacks opposing Pokémon by twanging a guitar or bass guitar, causing a huge echo and strong vibration."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_787">"The user attacks the target with an acidic liquid created from tart apples. This also lowers the target’s Sp. Def stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_788">"The user inflicts damage by dropping an apple from high above. This also lowers the target’s Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_789">"The user attacks the target with so much force that it could break the target’s spirit. This also lowers the target’s Sp. Atk stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_790">"The user attacks the target by emitting steam. This may also confuse the target." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_791">"The user scatters mysterious water around and restores the HP of itself and its ally Pokémon in the battle."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_792">"This move enables the user to protect itself from all attacks. Its chance of failing rises if it is used in succession. Direct contact harshly lowers the attacker’s Defense stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_793">"The user pretends to bow its head, but then it stabs the target with its disheveled hair. This attack never misses."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_794">"The user attacks wildly with its thick leek. The user can’t move on the next turn, because the force of this move makes it stagger." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_795">"This is Eternatus’s most powerful attack in its original form. The user can’t move on the next turn." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_796">"The user fires a beam of steel that it collected from its entire body. This also damages the user."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_797">"The user attacks the target with its psychic power. This move’s power goes up and damages all opposing Pokémon on Psychic Terrain." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_798">"The user attacks while destroying the terrain. This move fails when the ground hasn’t turned into a terrain."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_799">"The user attacks by shooting scales two to five times in a row. This move boosts the user’s Speed stat but lowers its Defense stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_800">"In this two-turn attack, the user gathers space power and boosts its Sp. Atk stat, then attacks the target on the next turn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_801">"This move inflicts physical or special damage, whichever will be more effective. This may also poison the target."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_802">"The user attacks everything around it and faints upon using this move. This move’s power is increased on Misty Terrain." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_803">"Gliding on the ground, the user attacks the target. This move always goes first on Grassy Terrain."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_804">"The user attacks with electric voltage rising from the ground. This move’s power doubles when the target is on Electric Terrain."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_805">"The user utilizes the power of the terrain to attack. This move’s type and power changes depending on the terrain when it’s used." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_806">"The user skitters behind the target to attack. This also lowers the target’s Sp. Atk stat."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_807">"The user attacks with energy from jealousy. This leaves all opposing Pokémon that have had their stats boosted during the turn with a burn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_808">"The user lashes out to vent its frustration toward the target. If the user’s stats were lowered during this turn, the power of this move is doubled." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_809">"The user attacks the target by controlling the target’s item. The move fails if the target doesn’t have an item." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_810">"The user surrounds everything around it with highly acidic gas and melts away items they hold." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_811">"The user properly coaches its ally Pokémon, boosting their Attack and Defense stats." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_812">"After making its attack, the user rushes back to switch places with a party Pokémon in waiting." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_813">"A consecutive three-kick attack that becomes more powerful with each successful hit." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_814">"The user slams the target with its wings. The target is hit twice in a row." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_815">"The user throws scorching sand at the target to attack. This may also leave the target with a burn."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_816">"The user becomes one with the jungle, restoring HP and healing any status conditions of itself and its ally Pokémon in battle."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_817">"The user, having mastered the Dark style, strikes the target with a fierce blow. This attack always results in a critical hit."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_818">"The user, having mastered the Water style, strikes the target with a flowing motion three times in a row. This attack always results in a critical hit." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_819">"The user traps the target in a cage of sparking electricity for four to five turns."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_820">"Converting its life-force into power, the user attacks opposing Pokémon. The lower the user’s HP, the lower the move’s power." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_821">"The user shoots its psychic power from its eyes to attack. This may also leave the target frozen." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_822">"The user transforms its wrath into a fire-like aura to attack. This may also make opposing Pokémon flinch."</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_823">"The user overwhelms the target with lightning-like movement before delivering a kick. This also lowers the target’s Defense stat." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_824">"The user attacks by hurling a blizzard-cloaked icicle lance at opposing Pokémon." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_825">"The user attacks by sending a frightful amount of small ghosts at opposing Pokémon." </string>
    <string name="move_flavor_826">"The user attacks with its tremendous psychic power. This also removes 3 PP from the target’s last move."</string>

    <string name="move_flavor_10001">Shadow Rush</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10002">Shadow Blast</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10003">Shadow Blitz</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10004">Shadow Bolt</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10005">Shadow Break</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10006">Shadow Chill</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10007">Shadow End</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10008">Shadow Fire</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10009">Shadow Rave</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10010">Shadow Storm</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10011">Shadow Wave</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10012">Shadow Down</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10013">Shadow Half</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10014">Shadow Hold</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10015">Shadow Mist</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10016">Shadow Panic</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10017">Shadow Shed</string>
    <string name="move_flavor_10018">Shadow Sky</string>

</resources>